mcxstar.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | MCXStar : Online MCX Commodity Markets Live Update

## Privacy Policy

This policy covers how we treat personal information collected and received, including information about you that is personally identifiable but is not otherwise publicly available.We are collecting your information while registering you on our website.For your information below is how we use this information.

  *     [**Mcxstar.com** ](http://mcxstar.com/)collects personal information when you register or use mcxstar.com products or services or when you visit web pages or otherwise, which information may include but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, phone number, zip/pin code, etc. and other such information about you which is not otherwise publicly available. Besides, mcxstar.com automatically receives and records statistics on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, the page you request, etc.

  *     **Mcxstar.com** uses the above information for the general purposes, including but not limited, to fulfilling your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, or send emails containing advertisements/ newsletters/notifications.

  *     **Mcxstar.com** does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with third parties, except when specifically informed to you at the time of collection of the information and / or to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

**a)** We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with mcxstar.com under confidentiality agreements for the purpose of creating / modifying / maintaining the site. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share / use this information for any other purpose, except for that specifically authorised by mcxstar.com.

**b)** We respond to court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

**c)** We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of mcxstar.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

**d)** We transfer information about you if mcxstar.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, mcxstar.com will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online, in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the mcxstar.com services or sponsored advertisements, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the mcxstar.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your mcxstar.com account, without offering you the opportunity to stop receiving them.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your mcxstar.com Account Information is password-protected.

mcxstar.com may update this policy from time to time. We may notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your mcxstar.com account or by placing a notice on our site for a reasonable period of time.

If any person, firl, company or other website owner has some issue regarding ant content of our website (MCXSTAR.COM). He/She need to contact us in writting mail to : info@mcxstar.com we will review your problem and if we found some issue we will surely remove it within 7 days from our website.

Privacy Policy in mcxstar.com
